
question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they received.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
